Reut Greenberg

(. +972506864908

Reutish91@gmail.com



About Me

As an experienced educator with a profound love for both teaching and learning, I firmly believe that every individual possesses a unique skill set and requires a distinct approach to education. Recently began exploring the fields of web design and graphic design as a secondary profession. I am a social person with a great communication skills.

Language

- English (Fluent)
- Hebrew (Native)



Education

(2003 - 2009)

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Omer High School

Theater Major

(2014-2015)

THERAPEUTIC DOG TRAINING CERTIFICATE

Tel Aviv University **Broshim Campus**

(2015 - 2019)

PSYCHOLOGY DEGREE B.A

Achva College

(2019 - 2020)

SPECIAL EDUCATION B.ED

Achva College Internship at the Academy College Lewinsky (2020-2021)



Experience

(2020 - 2023)

HAIR TECHNICIAN

BHR Clinic Israel Tel Aviv

Preforming hair transplants

(2020 - 2021)

EDUCATOR

Ministry of Education -Magen Elementary School Tel Aviv

- An educator for second graders
- English teacher for ASD 4-5 graders Working with modern models, planning and performing teaching processes that include diverse learning in a classroom space adapted to each child, his needs and abilities

(2019)

ENGLISH TEACHER

Ministry of Education

• A teacher "Rainbow" project at the Ministry of Education for 6th graders who have difficulty in the English subject.

(2016 - 2019)

PRIVATE TEACHER

 Part time Teacher for Math and **English subjects**

(2015 - 2016)

TEACHER

Private school "The campus"

 A teacher for Math and English for arades 7-8